So, first let's add some math.
首先我们来看看数学
We're going to label the horizontal axis corresponding to the test by the variable x1,
我们要标记对应测试的横坐标 记作变量 x1
and the vertical axis corresponding to the grades by the variable x2.
对应测试的纵坐标 记作变量 x2
So this boundary line that separates the blue
所以这条分隔蓝点和红点的分界线
and the red points is going to have a linear equation.
可以用线性方程表示
The one drawn has equation 2x1+x2-18=0.
这条线可以是方程式 2x1+x2-18=0
What does this mean?
这是什么意思呢？
This means that our method for accepting or rejecting students
这说明我们接受或拒绝学生的方法
simply says the following: take this equation as our score,
简单来说 把这个方程结果作为我们的分数
the score is 2xtest+grades-18.
Score = 2*Test+Grades-18
Now when the student comes in, we check their score.
每当输入学生的数据 我们就计算他们的分数
If their score is a positive number,
如果他们的分数为正
then we accept the student and if the score is
那么我们会接受这个学生
a negative number then we reject the student.
如果分数为负 那么我们拒绝这个学生
This is called a prediction.
这叫做预测
We can say by convention that if the score is 0,
根据惯例 如果分数为 0
we'll accept a student although this won't matter much at the end.
我们也会接受学生 虽然最后这样不会产生太大影响
And that's it. That linear equation is our model.
就是这样 线性方程是我们的模型
In the more general case, our boundary will be an equation of the following wx1+w2x2+b=0.
在更普遍的情况中 我们的边界线可能是以下这种方程 w1x1+w2x2+b=0
We'll abbreviate this equation in vector notation as wx+b=0,
我们用向量记法简化这个方程为 Wx+b=0
where w is the vector w1w2 and x is the vector x1x2.
其中 W 是向量 (w1,w2) x 是向量 (x1,x2)
And we simply take the product of the two vectors.
然后我们只需要得到两个向量的乘积
We'll refer to x as the input,
我们把 x 作为输入
to w as the weights and b as the bias.
W 作为权重 b 作为偏差
Now, for a student coordinates x1x2,
现在对于一个学生的坐标 (x1,x2)
we'll denote a label as Y and the label is what we're trying to predict.
我们用一个标签表示 y 这个标签是我们要预测的内容
So if the student gets accepted,
那么如果学生得到接受
namely the point is blue,
即为蓝点
then the label is Y+1.
那么标签是 Y=1
And if the student gets rejected,
那么如果学生被拒绝
namely the point is red and then the label is Y=0.
即为红点 标签为 Y=0
Thus, each point is in the form
所以每个点以 (x1,x2) 进行表示
x1x2Y or Y is 1 for the blue points and 0 for the red points.
蓝点时 Y=1 红点时 Y=0
And finally, our prediction is going to be called Y-hat and it will
最后我们得到的预测称为 Y-hat
be what the algorithm predicts that the label will be.
这是算法所预测的标签结果
In this case, Y-hat is one of the algorithm predicts that the student gets accepted,
在这个例子中如果这个算法预测到学生被接受 那么 Y-hat 为 1
which means the point lies over the line.
即点位于线段上方
And, Y-hat is 0 if the algorithm predicts that this didn't get rejected,
如果这个算法预测到学生被拒绝 那么 Y-hat 为 0
which means the point is under the line.
即点位于线段下方
In math terms, this means that the prediction Y-hat is 1 if wx+b
在数学项中 这表示如果 wx+b 大于或等于 0 那么 Y-hat 为 1
is greater than or equal to zero and 0 if wx+b is less than 0.
如果 wx+b 小于 0 那么 Y-hat 为 0
So, to summarize, the points above the line have
总之 点位于线段上方 那么 Y-hat 为 1
Y hat=1 and the points below the line have Y-hat=0.
点位于线段下方  那么 Y-hat 为 0
And, the blue points have Y=1 and the red points have Y=0.
蓝点得到 Y=1 红点得到 Y=0
And, the goal of the algorithm is to have Y-hat resembling Y as closely as possible,
这个算法的目的是让 Y-hat  尽量逼近 Y
which is exactly equivalent to finding the boundary line that keeps
这样相当于恰好找到边界线
most of the blue points above it and most of the red points below it.
让蓝点位于线段上方 红点位于线段下方